[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1304_1302_UndeadPresent",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1304_1302_d_00_container_UndeadPresent",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1304_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1304_1302_UndeadPresent_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1304_1302_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1304_1302_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1304_1302_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1304_1302_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1304_1302_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1304_1302_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1302_1304_BridgeOver",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1302_1304_d_00_container_BridgeOver",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1302_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1302_1304_BridgeOver_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1302_1304_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1302_1304_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1302_1304_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1302_1304_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1302_1304_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1302_1304_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1309_Possible",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1309_d_00_container_Possible",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1305_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_09",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1309_Possible_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1305_1309_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1305_1309_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1305_1309_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1305_1309_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1305_1309_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1305_1309_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1307_HazelsCave",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1307_d_00_container_HazelsCave",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1303_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1307_HazelsCave_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1303_1307_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1307_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1307_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1307_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1307_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1307_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1302_1305_HealingFeeling",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1302_1305_d_00_container_HealingFeeling",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1302_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1302_1305_HealingFeeling_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1302_1305_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1302_1305_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1302_1305_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1302_1305_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1302_1305_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1302_1305_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1306_Tarrying",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1306_d_00_container_Tarrying",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1310_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1306_Tarrying_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1310_1306_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1310_1306_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1310_1306_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1310_1306_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1310_1306_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1310_1306_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1308_Weavers",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1308_d_00_container_Weavers",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1305_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_05",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1308_Weavers_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1305_1308_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1305_1308_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1305_1308_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1305_1308_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1305_1308_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1305_1308_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1304_1303_GuardianFuture",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1304_1303_d_00_container_GuardianFuture",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1304_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_08",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1304_1303_GuardianFuture_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1304_1303_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1304_1303_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1304_1303_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1304_1303_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1304_1303_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1304_1303_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1310_Honoring",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1310_d_00_container_Honoring",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1303_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1310_Honoring_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1303_1310_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1310_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1310_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1310_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1310_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1310_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1304_1301_GhostsPast",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1304_1301_d_00_container_GhostsPast",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1304_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1304_1301_GhostsPast_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1304_1301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1304_1301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1304_1301_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1304_1301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1304_1301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1304_1301_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "WeaversFenArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1322_1316_d_00_container_ReprieveforRestless",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1522_Innkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Title",
        "Description": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1322_1316_ReprieveforRestless_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1302_1312_Spores",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1302_1312_d_00_container_Spores",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1302_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 49,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1302_1312_Spores_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1302_1312_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1302_1312_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1302_1312_b_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1302_1312_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1302_1312_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1302_1312_f_Complete",
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1330_0201_startingthefire",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1330_0201_d_00_container_startingthefire",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1330_Pyro",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1330_0201_startingthefire_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_title",
        "Description": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1330_0201_startingthefire_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1330_0202_burningfromtheinside",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1330_0202_d_00_container_burningfromtheinside",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1330_Pyro",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_title",
        "Description": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1330_0202_burningfromtheinside_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1330_0203_d_00_container_hellfirebrimstoneoven",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1330_Pyro",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_title",
        "Description": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1330_0203_hellfirebrimstoneoven_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1331_0201_fentonsfiend",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1331_0201_d_00_container_fentonsfiend",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1331_MonsterHunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1331_0201_fentonsfiend_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_title",
        "Description": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1331_0201_fentonsfiend_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1331_0202_keepingthefaith",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1331_0202_d_00_container_keepingthefaith",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1331_MonsterHunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1331_0202_keepingthefaith_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_title",
        "Description": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1331_0202_keepingthefaith_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1331_0204_extremeexorcism",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1331_0204_d_00_container_extremeexorcism",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1331_MonsterHunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1331_0204_extremeexorcism_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_title",
        "Description": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1331_0204_extremeexorcism_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1332_0201_gatorsgonewild",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1332_0201_d_00_container_gatorsgonewild",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1332_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_title",
        "Description": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1332_0201_gatorsgonewild_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1332_0202_thosedamnedboar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1332_0202_d_00_container_thosedamnedboar",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1332_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_title",
        "Description": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1332_0202_thosedamnedboar_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1332_0203_packfromhell",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1332_0203_d_00_container_packfromhell",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1332_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1332_0203_packfromhell_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_title",
        "Description": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1332_0203_packfromhell_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1332_0204_packleader",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1332_0204_d_00_container_packleader",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1332_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1332_0204_packleader_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1332_0204_packleader_title",
        "Description": "@1332_0204_packleader_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1332_0204_packleader_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1332_0204_packleader_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1332_0204_packleader_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1332_0204_packleader_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1333_0201_agelessedifice",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1333_0201_d_00_container_agelessedifice",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1333_Architect",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1333_0201_agelessedifice_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_title",
        "Description": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1333_0201_agelessedifice_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1333_0202_spanningtheages",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1333_0202_d_00_container_spanningtheages",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1333_Architect",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1333_0202_spanningtheages_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_title",
        "Description": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1333_0202_spanningtheages_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1333_0203_timelesstower",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1333_0203_d_00_container_timelesstower",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1333_Architect",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1333_0203_timelesstower_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_title",
        "Description": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1333_0203_timelesstower_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1334_0201_d_00_container_olfactoryoptimization",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1334_Alchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_31",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_title",
        "Description": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1334_0201_olfactoryoptimization_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1335_0201_misplacedtreasure",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1335_0201_d_00_container_misplacedtreasure",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1335_Antiquarian",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_title",
        "Description": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1335_0201_misplacedtreasure_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1335_0202_canopus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1335_0202_d_00_container_canopus",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1335_Antiquarian",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1335_0202_canopus_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1335_0202_canopus_title",
        "Description": "@1335_0202_canopus_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1335_0202_canopus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1335_0202_canopus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1335_0202_canopus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1335_0202_canopus_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1335_0203_lasluswell",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1335_0203_d_00_container_lasluswell",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1336_AntiquarianSpouse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1335_0203_lasluswell_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_title",
        "Description": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1335_0203_lasluswell_complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1335_0204_reunion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 38,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1335_0204_d_00_container_reunion",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1335_Antiquarian",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1335_0204_reunion_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1335_0204_reunion_title",
        "Description": "@1335_0204_reunion_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1335_0204_reunion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1335_0204_reunion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1335_0204_reunion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1335_0204_reunion_complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1303_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 38,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_Protective_Wyrd_Gear_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_01_Shoes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_01_Shoes_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_Boots",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_01_Shoes_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_01_Shoes_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_02_Shirt",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_02_Shirt_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_Shirt",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_02_Shirt_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_02_Shirt_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_03_Pants",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_03_Pants_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_Pants",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_03_Pants_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_03_Pants_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_04_Gloves",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_04_Gloves_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_Gloves",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_04_Gloves_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_04_Gloves_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1303_1311_05_Hat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1303_1311_05_Hat_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_Armor_11_Hat",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1303_1311_05_Hat_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Title",
        "Description": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1303_1311_05_Hat_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1310_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 38,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1310_1314_L40Bow_Huntress_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_AncientWood_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1314_AncientWood_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_AncientWood_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_AncientWood_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_AncientWood_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_WyrdwoodResin_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1314_WyrdwoodResin_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_WyrdwoodResin_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_WyrdwoodResin_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_WyrdwoodResin_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_HawkFeathers_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1314_HawkFeathers_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_HawkFeathers_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_HawkFeathers_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_HawkFeathers_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1310_1314_LuckyRabbitsFoot_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1310_1314_LuckyRabbitsFoot_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TheHuntress_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1310_1314_LuckyRabbitsFoot_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1310_1314_LuckyRabbitsFoot_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1310_1314_LuckyRabbitsFoot_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1305_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_10",
        "RequiredLevel": 38,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1305_1315_L40FStaff_FalmeasWrath_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_SingedBranches_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1315_SingedBranches_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_01",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_SingedBranches_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_SingedBranches_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_SingedBranches_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_WyrdwoodAshes_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1315_WyrdwoodAshes_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_02",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_WyrdwoodAshes_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_WyrdwoodAshes_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_WyrdwoodAshes_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_UnhallowedWater_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1315_UnhallowedWater_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_03",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_UnhallowedWater_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_UnhallowedWater_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_UnhallowedWater_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1305_1315_HeartofAllFlame_Quest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1305_1315_HeartofAllFlame_Quest_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_FalmeasWrath_04",
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1305_1315_HeartofAllFlame_Quest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1305_1315_HeartofAllFlame_Quest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1305_1315_HeartofAllFlame_Quest_description"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1301_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1301_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1302_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1302_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1303_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1303_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1304_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1304_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1305_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1305_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1306_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1306_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1307_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1307_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1308_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1308_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1309_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1309_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1310_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1310_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1361_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1361_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1362_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1362_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1363_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1363_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1364_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1364_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1365_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1365_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1366_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1366_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1367_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1367_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1368_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1368_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1369_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1369_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1370_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1370_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_PoachSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_13_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_13_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_13_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_13_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_13_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 13,
        "RequiredLevel": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]